Let's see the code we have so far in action.
これまでのコードを実行しましょう
First, we define here our feature columns,
まずここでfeature_columnを定義します
one numeric column for square footage,
面積のnumeric_columnが1つ
and one categorical column with the caber list for the property type house, or apartment.
物件タイプ（戸建てまたはアパート）の categorical_column_with_vocaburary_listです
We will also have to provide data formatted in the same way.
同じ形式に設定されたデータを提供します
We do this through this training input function here.
このtrain_input関数でそれを行います
Our features as defined below,
下で定義しているように
will be square footage.
特徴（features）は面積です
Here is a less list of six species of data.
6つのデータからなるリストです
The property type again,
そして再び物件タイプです
a list of six property types,
6つの物件タイプからなるリストで
three houses, three apartments.
3つの戸建てと3つのアパートです
And finally our target labels,
最後にターゲットとなるlabelsは
which are property prices here in thousands of dollars.
1,000ドル単位の物件価格です
Now that we have this training input functions and the feature columns,
こうしてtrain_input関数と feature_columnができたので
we are ready to instantiate a linear regressor.
LinearRegressorをインスタンス化できます
That's one of the premade estimators,
作成済みEstimatorです
and start training by calling
トレーニングを開始するために
model.train and passing the training input function as a parameter.
model.trainを呼び出し train_input関数をパラメータとして渡します
You see training happening here,
トレーニングがこうして行われます
and when it's done,
完了したら
we can try to predict something.
予測を試してみましょう
So, for that we need a predict input function,
それにはpredict_input関数が必要です
which will fit in our features,
今回の特徴に合わせて
square footage and type.
square_footageとtypeを使います
I define it here and I call model.predict with this predict input function.
predict_input関数を定義し それを使ってmodel.predictを呼び出します
It gives me a predictions generator.
これで予測ジェネレーターができました
This is a python generator.
Pythonのジェネレーターです
Let's do that. And here we go,
やってみましょう できました